我在部队长大 工作 总被派去不同的地方 要求准时报到
Grew up in the military, worked in the military.
现在我按自己的心意 好好看看这个国家
Always told where to go, when to be there. I want to see my country on my own terms.
住汽车旅馆 随身携带现金 用假名 轻装旅行
Motels, cash, fake names, travel light.
你会习惯的
You get used to it.
搜索他的指纹没有发现案底 不过还是应该有所发现的
So far, a run on his prints has been clean, but something could still turn up.
没有驾照 抵押贷款 保险索赔
No driver's license, mortgage, insurance claims.
根本没有在线个人资料
No online profile at all.
杰克雷彻存在的唯一证据 就是他坐在那个房间里面
The only proof Jack Reacher exists is the fact that he's sitting in that room.
在你执行任务的过程中干掉了几个人
Took out a few men in the course of your duties.
所有都被裁定为有正当理由
All ruled good kills.
曾经领导宪兵队的110
Commanded the 110th Special Investigations Unit
特别调查组
of the Military Police.
十万年前
100,000 years ago,
就有些人会留在篝火旁 还有些人会去流浪
there were people who stayed by the campfire and people who wandered.
我很确定我是流浪族群的直系后代
I'm pretty sure I'm a direct descendant of the wandering type.
这是我的本性
It's just who I am.
纽约卡兹奇山 曼哈顿以北两小时车程处
烈探雷彻
第二季第一集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
阿肯色州默弗里斯伯勒
我该怎么处置这些衣服
What am I supposed to do with these?
洗干净然后卖掉 你这是家二手店
Wash them and sell them. You're a thrift store.
- 你要买什么东西吗  - 买我穿的这身
You buying anything? What I'm wearing.
牛仔裤 T恤 夹克 袜子 平角裤
Jeans, T-shirt, jacket, socks, boxers.
22美元
$22.
所有物品 五折优惠
Eleven.
嗯 道格几天前就该 把那个折扣标签撤掉了 是22美元
Yeah, Doug was supposed to take that down a few days ago. It's $22.
那你为什么不把它撤下来
If you knew they were supposed to come down, why didn't you do it?
因为这是道格的工作
'Cause it's Doug's job.
街对面有个自动提款机
There's an ATM across the street.
这是我的护照 这样你就不用担心我跑单了
I'll leave you my passport so you know I'm not running off.
你跑了我也不在乎 这工作太垃圾了
Don't care if you do. This job is shit.
对不起 我必须再取一笔
Sorry, I have to make another withdrawal.
别回头 我可以帮你
Don't turn around. I can help you.
继续取钱
Keep taking out money.
我左边的小面包车 那是你的车
That minivan to my left... that yours?
是的
Yes.
我先了解清楚 你被劫车了 对吧
Just for clarity, you've been carjacked, right?
- 我的孩子在后座 - 有枪
My child is in the back seat. Gun?
是的
Yes.
待在这里 用不了太久
Stay here. This won't take long.
快啊
Come on...
孩子 你妈最好动作快点 否则你们俩就惨了
Your mom better hurry the fuck up, kid, or this is gonna go bad for both of you.
嗨 想见你妈妈吗
Hi. Want to see your mom?
没事了 宝贝
It's okay. It's okay.
亲爱的 没事了 我在这
Come here. It's okay. I mean, I'm here. Oh, baby.
那家伙会昏迷一会儿
That guy will be out for a while.
去银行报警 把这些给他们
Go in the bank, call the cops, give them these.
枪在车里
Gun's in the car.
等等 你是谁
Wait. Who are you?
一个不想被牵涉进去的人
Someone who prefers not getting involved.
这是30美元 我需要一件新夹克
Here's $30. Need a new jacket.
你刚买的那件怎么了
What's wrong with the one you just bought?
上面沾了血
It has blood on it.
我能借用你的手机吗
Can I use your phone?
我刚收到朋友发来的消息
I just got a message from a friend.
塔米凯茨
"Tammi Cates"?
让我猜猜 是银行柜员 餐厅服务员还是二手店收银员
Let me guess. Bank teller, diner waitress, thrift shop cashier?
第三个 我收到你的消息了
Third one. I got your message.
110特别调查组 “10-30”
110th. 10-30.
这是求救信号
A distress call.
是求救信号以及机票
Distress call and airfare.
- 我需要你尽快来纽约 - 为什么
I need you to come to New York ASAP. Why?
卡尔文弗朗茨被谋杀了
Calvin Franz was murdered.
我下了飞机会通知你的
I'll let you know when I land.
弗吉尼亚州岩溪 (几年前)
雷彻少校
Major Reacher.
您好 长官
Hello, sir.
叫我雷彻就好 我没让你带任何东西
Just Reacher. I didn't tell you to bring anything.
只是一些办公用品 以防万一要做启动文书工作
Oh, um, just some office supplies, in case there was any start-up paperwork needed to be done.
我讨厌文书工作
- I hate paperwork. - That's okay,
我倒是不介意做文书工作 长官
I don't mind doing any clerical there might be, sir.
- 叫我雷彻 - 对了 雷彻
- Reacher. - Uh, r-right. Reacher.
希望你不介意我这么问 我到底是来干什么的
Um, I hope you don't mind my asking, what exactly am I doing here?
- 弗朗茨 你已经想退出了  - 不是的 长官...雷彻
- Want out already, Franz? - No, sir. Um, Reacher.
我没想退出 我只是很好奇
Uh, no. I-I don't. I'm just curious is all.
几周前 我在你的军营里见过你
Saw you a few weeks ago by your barracks.
你当时阻止了几个士兵 为从家里偷来的护理包打架
Stopped a couple soldiers from beating the hell of each other over a stolen care package from home.
实际上是盒子里的最后一块饼干
Last cookie in the box, actually.
一块饼干
One cookie?
- 是啊 - 那更蠢了
- Yeah. - Even dumber.
至少 你谈判出了 一个公平的解决方案
Bottom line, you negotiated a fair settlement,
开了几个玩笑 缓解了冲突
cracked a few jokes, de-escalated the conflict.
你的脑子转得挺快 可能会派上用场
Got a decent head on you. Might come in handy.
好吧 我得问问
Okay, I got to ask,
雷彻少校到底在这里 组建了一支什么样的队伍
what the hell kind of unit did Major Reacher put together here, huh?
我们有从会计部找来的会计
We got a bean counter from Accounting Services,
散装燃料公司的加油站员工
a gas jockey from bulk fuel,
我们有音乐才子
we got Dave Matthews,
摩西爷爷 还有几个人 来自...
Grandpa Moses and, uh, a couple of guys from, uh...
你们都是从哪儿来的  我在采购部见过你们 对吧
where y'all from? I've seen you in Requisitions, right?
我们有名字
We've got names.
桑切斯和奥罗斯科
Sanchez and Orozco.
哪个是奥罗斯科
Which one's Orozco?
除了话痨 你又是什么人
And who are you, besides a guy who talks too much?
大卫奥唐纳
David O'Donnell.
无意冒犯 老大爷 但你来这里做什么
And no offense, Pops, but, uh, why are you here?
你是错过了老年电视剧还是怎么着
Isn't there a CBS drama you're missing?
劳莱曾六次赢得陆军
Lowrey won the Army Marksmanship competition
手枪和步枪射击比赛
six times, both pistol and rifle class.
我有个规矩
I've got a rule.
一旦打出第一枪 计划就见鬼去吧
Plans go to hell soon as first shot's been fired,
所以你们的第一枪 最好是打得最准的一枪
so your first shot better be your best shot.
我是唯一一个赢得 千码邀请赛的非海军队员
I'm the only non-Marine to win the USMC 1,000 Yard Invitational,
而且我都知道劳莱 是我们最厉害的“第一枪”
and I still know Lowrey gives us our best first shot.
你觉得这支队伍会遭受枪击
You think this unit's gonna come under a lot of fire?
说不准
Maybe.
那你为什么要找 没有警察经历的人来 雷彻少校
Then why'd you grab a bunch of people with no police experience, Major Reacher?
- 叫我雷彻 - 叫他雷彻
- Reacher. - Reacher.
对不起
Sorry.
军队需要一支 专门处理复杂事务的队伍
Army wanted a unit for particularly complex matters when they arose.
为此 我需要特别调查员 不是一般的宪兵
To do that, I need special investigators, not generic MPs.
如果我们那么特别 那为什么给我们的办公室这么垃圾
If we're so special, why did they stick us in this dump?
这地方是怎么回事
I mean, what is up with this place?
几年前 山姆大叔 出价购买了这条街上的一些土地
Few years ago, Uncle Sam made an auction bid for some land down the road.
地址输反了
Entered the address backwards
就成了这栋建筑的骄傲的主人 而且还成了现已结业的
and became the proud owners of this building and the contents
卡拉翰保险公司的所有人
of the now-defunct Callahan Insurance Agency.
但你说得对 办公地点可以更好一点
But you're right. Place could work a little better.
整理好这些箱子
Straighten up these boxes,
把这些旧桌子移到房间中间
move these old tanker desks to the middle of the room.
动手吧
Let's go.
你们不必叫我少校
You don't have to call me "Major,"
但我让你们行动时 你们必须动起来 开始吧
but you do have to move your ass when I say so. Get to it.
向后退
Go backwards.
你想让我向后退
Okay, you want me to go backwards?
- 我要向后退 - 向后退
- I'm going backwards. - Go back.
- 腿用力 抬起来 - 没人用腿抬
Lift with your legs, man! No one lifts with their legs.
数到三 一 二 三 抬
On three. One, two, three, go.
你这么抬不对
You're doing it wrong.
我是按你说的做的
I'm doing it exactly how you told me to.
你觉得我们真能一起工作
You think we're actually gonna be able to work together?
腿用力 抬起来
我不知道
No idea.
但我可以请大家喝酒
But I could use a beer.
跟他们说我买单
Tell them I'm buying.
威廉斯堡 纽约布鲁克林
雷彻
Reacher.
内格利
Neagley.
谢谢你点餐 杯子里还冒着热气
Thanks for ordering. Still steam coming off the cup.
我在网上追踪了航班信息 看到它提前落地了
Tracked the plane online, saw it landed early,
你不托运行李 我算了通勤时间
you don't check bags and I adjusted for traffic.
90秒前倒的咖啡
Had the coffee poured 90 seconds ago.
食物已经上桌三分钟了
Food's been there three minutes.
非常感谢
Appreciated.
这是从哪儿弄到的
Where'd you get this?
我是私家侦探 能搜集到这些东西
I'm a PI. I can get things.
距离马格雷夫一别有些时日了
Been a minute since Margrave.
是两年七个月19天
Been two years, seven months, 19 days.
你气色不错
You look good.
我看起来没变化
I look the same.
跟两年七个月19天前一样好
You looked good two years, seven months, 19 days ago,
所以你看起来也一样
so, yeah. You look the same.
你看起来鞍马劳顿
You look... road-worn.
是啊
Yep.
那么 弗朗茨 给我讲讲大体情况
So, Franz. Give me the Cliff Notes.
大约一周前 他离家后失踪了
Went missing after leaving his home in Brooklyn about a week or so ago.
尸体被发现于卡兹奇山
Body was found in the Catskill Mountains.
整个警察局有20名警察
Whole force up there is, like, 20 cops.
弗朗茨在城里失踪后 纽约市警察局开始牵头调查
And since Franz disappeared in the city, NYPD's taking the lead.
- 你是怎么知道的  - 安吉拉给我打了电话
How'd you find out? Got a call from Angela.
- 弗朗茨的遗孀 - 弗朗茨结婚了
Franzy's widow.  Franz was married?
是啊 很有趣的婚礼 还有巧克力喷泉
Yeah. Fun wedding. Chocolate fountain.
他还有个儿子
He had a son, too.
怎么了 大块头 你不在的时候 生活还在继续
What? Life moves on when you're away, big fella.
还有什么消息
What else?
他失踪前几天给我留了几条信息
Franz left me a few messages in the days before his disappearance.
想从我这里了解一些 他正在追查的案件的信息
Said he wanted to bounce some stuff off of me about a case he was chasing down.
我当时忙着做自己的工作 我一直想回去找他来着
I was so tied up with my own work, I kept meaning to get back to him, but...
但在我找他之前 安吉拉联系我 说他被杀了
before I could, Angela reached out and told me he'd been murdered.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
- 我知道 - 他不仅仅是被谋杀
- I know. - He wasn't just murdered.
还受到了折磨
He was tortured.
他的胃里只有粘液 脱水了 没有食物 没有水
Nothing but mucus in his stomach. Dehydrated. No food, no water.
他被扔出了飞机
Chucked out of a plane.
他们不可能是把他扔下飞机的
They didn't throw him from a plane.
他的尸体被发现于荒无人烟的地方
He was found in the middle of nowhere with injuries
受伤情况跟从一公里的高处 坠落的伤口相吻合
consistent with a fall from 3,000 feet.
飞机的失速速度是多少来着  每小时130公里 最高160公里
An airplane has a stall speed of what? 80 miles an hour? 100, tops?
他们会垂直把他扔到气流中
They would've shoved him out of the door's plane horizontally into the slipstream.
他会撞到机翼或机尾
He'd bang into the wing or tail.
那样会造成死前伤口 但他身上没有
There'd be perimortem injuries and there aren't.
他是被从直升机上扔下来的
He was thrown from a helicopter.
- 他的腿骨折不是坠地造成的 - 此话怎讲
His broken legs weren't from the fall, anyway. Because?
看他的血液检查结果
Look at his blood work.
充满了游离组胺 这反映出了剧烈的疼痛反应
Full of free histamines. Massive pain reaction.
直到死前 游离组胺的含量都极高
You don't get these kind of levels from injuries sustained at the time of death.
断腿是几天前的事
Broken legs were a few days old.
因此 在他裤子的布料中 发现了氧化亚铁粉
That's why ferrous oxide powder was found in his pants fabric.
他曾被一根生锈的铁棒击中
He was hit with a rusty iron bar.
一定疼死了
Must've hurt like hell.
是啊 他要么是因为报复而被折磨 要么是因为情报
Yep. He was tortured for either revenge or information.
凶手得手以后 把他从空中丢出 避免了使用枪支
When they were done with him, they dumped him from the sky to avoid ballistics.
几个大学生在徒步的时候 发现了尸体
Couple of college kids wandered off their hiking trail, saw the body.
否则谁知道他什么时候才会被发现
If not for them, who knows when he would've been found?
那么 接下来呢
So, next steps?
如果他给你打过电话 那他可能也给队里其他人打过
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
大概是失败了
Probably failed.
我给奥唐纳 迪克森 桑切斯和奥罗斯科打了电话
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco.
都没人接
No one's answering.
斯旺没有登记电话号码 连我的办公室都找不到他的电话
No listed number for Swan. Even my office can't find it.
他总是非常注重隐私 劳莱呢
Always a private guy. What about Lowrey?
他两年前死于蒙大拿的一场车祸
Killed two years ago in a car accident in Montana.
葬礼非常伤感 但很高兴再次见到这伙人
Funeral was sad, but... it was good to see the gang again.
我猜你不在的时候 有些人也走向了终点
Guess life ends when you're away, too.
弗朗茨的婚礼 劳莱的葬礼 全都没人告诉我
Franz's wedding, Lowrey's funeral. No one told me.
没有电话 没有地址
No phone, no address.
你本来可以像今天一样 给我发一条紧急取款机信息
You could've sent me an emergency ATM message like today.
首先 我刚想到这个方法
First off, I just thought of that.
其次 那也不是紧急情况
Second, it wasn't really an emergency.
紧急的是卡车撞上劳莱的那一刻
The emergency was the moment the pickup hit Lowrey.
而且说实话 你真的愿意 大老远地从德州或缅因州
And be honest, would you really have travelled all the way to Montana
或你当时所在的地方赶到蒙大拿
from Texas or Maine or wherever you were at the time
就为了看一眼盒子里的尸体
just to look at a body in a box?
不愿意
No.
那我再问一次 接下来呢
So I'll ask again. Next steps?
你真的想让其他警察 去处理我们死去的朋友的案子
You really want to let some other cops handle our dead friend's case?
我也这么想
That's what I thought.
我们去见见弗朗茨的遗孀吧
Let's go see Franzy's widow.
她刚跟大块头见了面
She just met up with the big one.
我是大卫奥唐纳 我现在不在
You've reached David O'Donnell. I'm not around;
请留言 我会回电
leave a message. I'll call you back.
奥唐纳 我是雷彻 现在急需帮忙
O'Donnell. This is Reacher with another 10-30.
内格利和我住在布鲁克林的瓦尔酒店
Neagley and I are staying at the Vale Hotel in Brooklyn.
快行动 给我们回电
Get off your ass and call us back.
我们没法给斯旺打电话
So, we can't call Swan.
奥唐纳 桑切斯和奥罗斯科 还是不接电话
O'Donnell, Sanchez and Orozco still don't answer.
迪克森办公室的接待员
And the receptionist at Dixon's office says
说她不知道她在哪儿 也不知道她何时回来
she can't say where Dixon is or when she'll return.
可能是在做卧底工作
Probably an undercover job.
也许吧
Maybe.
也许他们也遇到麻烦了
Or maybe they're all in trouble, too.
米奇 去拿你的蜡笔 玩填色游戏 好吗
Mikey. Go find your crayons and do some coloring time, okay?
请坐
Please sit.
抱歉我过了这么久才脱身
Sorry it took me so long to disengage.
让我姐姐挂断电话很难
It's just hard to get my sister off the phone.
她每小时打一次电话 是我的个人自杀督查表
She calls every hour. My own personal suicide watch.
抱歉 那是种病 我不应该说那话
Sorry. That was, uh, morbid. I shouldn't have said that.
你经历了那些事 想说什么都行
After what you've been through, you can say whatever you want.
你的儿子竟然长得那么像弗朗茨
Can't believe how much your son looks like Franzy.
我也叫他弗朗茨
I called him Franzy, too.
是你们中的哪个 给他起的名字来着 我忘了
Which one of you gave him that name again? I forgot.
奥唐纳
O'Donnell.
对 大卫奥唐纳
Right. David O'Donnell.
他曾经叫你“大块头”
And he used to call you The Big Guy.
我的天啊 卡尔文 给我讲过你们所有人的故事
My God, did Calvin ever tell me stories about you all.
我知道他爱我和米奇胜过一切
I know he loved me and Mikey more than anything,
但从他说话的方式来看 我觉得他更享受
but from the way he talked, I don't think he ever ad any more fun
他在110组里度过的时光
than his years spent with the 110th.
这可说不准 自从你们在一起后
I don't know about that. Ever since you guys got together,
每当我跟他聊天时 他看上去都很高兴
whenever I talked to him, he seemed joyful.
比我认识的他更加高兴
Happier than I ever knew him.
谢谢你这么说
Thank you f-for saying that.
我知道警方已经问过你一大堆问题了
I know the police have already asked you a million questions,
但你能讲讲时间线吗
but do you think you could walk us through the time line?
当然
Sure.
我当时跟米奇在普洛佛
I was away with Mikey in Provo,
帮姐姐照顾我们的妈妈
helping my sister with our mom.
她有早发性痴呆
Early-onset dementia.
我试着联系了卡尔文几天 但他没有回电话
I tried Calvin for a few days, and no return calls.
这不像他的作风 所以我开始担心
It's not like him, so I started to worry.
我给纽约警局打电话
Called NYPD,
他们说他可能是出去查案子了 因为他是一名私家侦探
they just said he could've been out on a case because he was a PI
或者他可能出去参加派对了 因为他的老婆和孩子不在
or maybe he was out partying because his wife and kid were out of town.
你觉得他是去做那事了吗  出去跟损友聚会
Do you think that's what he was doing? Out partying with the wrong crowd?
卡尔文连晚餐迟到十分钟 都会给我打电话
Cal would call if he was gonna be ten minutes late for dinner.
他不会跟别人参加派对
And he didn't party with anybody.
所以我很担心 我提早回来 发现我们家被搜了个遍
So I got so worried, I came back early to find our home ransacked.
什么都没被拿走
Nothing was taken.
警察不知道是谁干的
The cops have no idea who did it.
你知道他可能在查什么案子吗
Were you aware of any cases Franz may have been working on?
他从不把工作带回家
He never brought work home.
他说他在家的时候
He said when he was here,
希望把百分之百的心思花在我
he wanted to be 100% present for me,
还有米奇身上
and Mikey.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想帮忙 这太难了
I want to help. It's just so hard.
每天都很痛苦
Every day hurts.
再问几个问题 我保证就几个
Just a few more questions. Promise.
好的
Okay.
他的客户群是什么样的
What was his client base like?
华尔街那种 首席执行官 对冲基金人群
Wall Street types. CEOs, the hedge fund crowd.
有特别难搞的客户吗  给他带来麻烦的 让他压力很大的
Any of them particularly rough? Causing him problems? Stressing him out?
一个都没有
No. Not at all. Once Mikey came along,
米奇一出生 他就不再做危险的工作了
he stopped doing the dangerous jobs.
现在看来并非如此
Or so I thought.
他跟110组的其他人有合作吗
Were any other members of the 110th working with him?
我不知道 也许他的办公室里有什么线索
I don't know. Maybe there's something in his office.
门上的招牌是三河咨询公司
Sign on the door is Three Rivers Consulting and Associates.
在弗拉特布什103号
It's 103 Flatbush. It was trashed, too.
办公室也被毁了 警察在那里一无所获
The cops couldn't find anything there,
但弗朗茨总是告诉我
but from what Franzy always told me,
特别调查员不是普通的警察
the Special Investigators weren't any old group of cops.
不要惹特别调查员
You do not mess with the Special Investigators.
你爸教你的
Your daddy teach you that?
你想知道你爸 是怎么成为特别调查员的吗
Do you want to know how your dad became a Special Investigator?
他阻止了两个大块头士兵之间的打斗
He stopped a fight between two huge soldiers
因为其中一人以为
because one of them thought the other had stolen
另一个人偷了他妈妈给他的 饼干盒里的最后一块自制饼干
the last homemade cookie sent to him from his mom.
你爸爸让他们握手言和 再次成为朋友
Your dad got them to shake hands and be friends again.
而这里的这个人
And this guy, right here,
他想让你爸爸加入110组 因为...
he wanted your dad to be part of the 110th because...
他发现了一个能在情况激烈时 保持冷静的人
...he saw a man who stayed cool when things got heated.
就这样 我们跟你爸成了朋友
That's how we became friends with your dad.
好的
Okay.
你知道是弗朗茨吃了饼干
You know Franz ate the cookie.
- 以为人人有份  - 是啊
- Thought it was for everyone? - Yup.
我很确定街上那辆黑色轿车
I'm pretty sure that black sedan halfway down the street
刚才我们吃饭时也在餐馆外
was outside the diner, too.
美国每条街道上都有黑色轿车 上车
There's a black sedan on every street in America. Get in.
- 经理说话了吗  - 没 我买通了门房
Did the manager talk? Nah, I paid off the concierge.
他指认内格利以莎拉寇娜的名字 登记入住
He ID'd Neagley as checking in under the name Sarah Conner
并且用史达林卡斯楚的名字 支付了隔壁房间的费用
and, uh, paying for an adjoining room using the name Starlin Castro.
一定是给大块头付的房费
That must be for the Hulk.
六七年前 史达林卡斯楚 曾效力于洋基队
Starlin Castro played for the Yankees, six or seven years ago.
对 莎拉寇娜是谁
And who's Sarah Conner?
我不在乎
I don't give a shit.
盯紧那家酒店还有他们
Just keep an eye on that hotel... and them.
收到
Copy that.
三河咨询公司
对于跟华尔街生意人士 打交道的人来说 这很低调
Pretty modest for a guy with Wall Street business.
朴实无华
Unpretentious.
离家近 这样他能多陪陪家人
Close to home so he can spend more time with his family.
正是弗朗茨会选的地方
Exact kind of place Franzy would choose.
安吉拉说办公室“被毁了” 她没开玩笑
Angela wasn't kidding when she said trashed.
他们可能什么都没发现
They probably didn't find anything.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
如果你能马上找到需要的东西 就不会这么大费周章
You don't go to this length if you found what you needed right away.
他们离开时很生气
And they left pissed.
他们没搜窗户后面 却用电话砸穿了
They weren't looking for anything behind this glass window, but they put that phone through it.
这是人没发现自己想找的东西时 沮丧的表现
That's an act of frustration by someone who didn't find what they wanted.
他们想要的东西很小
Whatever they wanted was small.
若不是要找能塞进椅子腿的东西
You don't snap chair legs in half to see
你不会折断椅子腿 来看它是否是空心的
if they've been hollowed out unless you're looking for something that can fit in there.
嘿
Hey.
看看这个
Check this out.
仿佛是昨天的事
Seems like yesterday.
钥匙链
Keychain?
弗朗茨很机警 对吧
Franz was sharp, right?
非常机警
Very sharp.
如果他要处理 可能会让自己丧命的东西
So if he was dealing with something that could get him killed,
他必须把它放在一个 安全但很容易获取的地方
he'd have to put it in a place that was very secure, but readily available.
我们每天都能见到
Somewhere in plain sight that we see every day,
但又不会引起别人怀疑的地方
but a place no one would suspect.
对
Okay.
所以什么地方是唾手可得
So what's a place that's readily available
可以将重要物品托付在那里的呢
that we entrust every day with very important items?
这是邮箱钥匙
This is a mailbox key.
美国邮政服务
我有没有说过你很聪明 内格利
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley?
还远远不够
Not nearly enough.
见鬼 已经五点过了
Shit. It's after 5:00.
如果是四位数密码 那有一万种组合
10,000 combinations if it's a four-number code.
- 尝试没有意义 - 很好
- No point in trying. - Good.
我很讨厌猜密码
Hate guessing passwords.
我们得明天再来
We'll have to come back tomorrow.
那我们现在干什么
So, what do we do now?
金
Gin.
我都不知道我为什么要玩
I don't even know why I play.
- 因为你抱着赢我的希望 - 我赢了几手牌
'Cause you hold out hope you'll beat me. I won a few hands.
如果你放水 我会生气的
If you let me win, I'm gonna be pissed.
我不会放水 我会慢慢调整我的节奏
I don't let you win. I pace myself.
你的职业生涯可不是这样的
Not in your professional life.
我没听懂
Don't follow.
租的车是辆路虎揽胜 非常棒的酒店房间
Rental car's a Range Rover, killer hotel rooms,
给我寄了机票 好像票不值钱一样
sent me airfare like it was nothing.
你事业很成功
You're doing well.
很明显在你的职业生涯中 你没慢慢调整节奏
Clearly not pacing yourself in your professional life.
不是我吹牛 “少年得志” 这个词已经在我办公室传开了
Not to brag, but the term "wunderkind" has been tossed around the office.
在过去的两年里 我两次升职
Two promotions in the past two years.
他们要在圣路易斯开一家分公司
They're opening a satellite office in St. Louis.
他们让我去当负责人
Offered me director if I wanted it.
但我太喜欢出外勤了
But I like being in the field too much.
出外勤做什么
Doing what?
主要是给高收入人群
Mostly investigative work for high-income individuals.
政府机构 家族企业之类的 做调查工作
Government entities, family offices, that kind of thing.
我们偶尔会接一些无偿的案子
Once in a while we do a pro bono case.
找失踪的孩子 被盗的艺术品
Missing kids, stolen artwork...
所以这不仅仅是为了赚钱
So, it's not just about the money.
感觉很不错
It feels good.
你呢
What about you?
不久前在苏福尔斯看了一场 小职业球队联盟的比赛
Saw a minor league game in Sioux Falls a while back.
真引人入胜
Riveting.
跟其他人一起看的
See it with anyone else?
不是
No.
你在看比赛时跟任何人说话了吗
Did you, uh... talk to anyone at the game?
我点了杯啤酒
I ordered a beer.
好吧
Okay.
说到跟人说话
Speaking of talking to people,
你出去加油的时候 我又试着给大家打了电话
when you went out to get gas, I tried everyone again.
无线电静默
Radio silence.
你给谁打得最多
Who'd you call the most?
桑切斯 奥罗斯科 奥唐纳
Sanchez? Orozco? O'Donnell?
还是迪克森
Or... Dixon?
她有接听应答服务
She has an answering service.
跟语音信箱不同 有人可以说话
Instead of leaving a voice mail, there's someone to actually talk to.
对 因为我们刚发现 你有多喜欢跟人聊天
Right. 'Cause we just established how much you like talking to people.
别说了
Shut up.
没关系
It's okay.
很明显你们俩对彼此都有好感
It was always obvious you guys had a thing for each other.
你们睡过了吗
Did you ever sleep together?
没
No.
- 为什么  - 那样不合适
Why not? Wouldn't have been appropriate.
你们是同一级别的
You were the same rank.
我负责管理团队
I ran the team.
不合适
Not appropriate.
但你觉得她很有魅力
But you found her attractive.
- 这不是有目共睹的事吗  - 我就不觉得
- Who wouldn't? - Me.
我没发现任何有魅力的人
I don't find anyone attractive.
金
Gin.
我要去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
我会把房费 机票钱 还有所有费用都还给你
I'll pay you back for the room and flight and everything.
大约一周后我就能收到养老金了
I get my pension deposit in about a week.
不需要
Not necessary.
如果我没被“雷彻学院”录取的话 就不会有现在的事业
I wouldn't have my career if I hadn't matriculated at the School of Reacher.
就当是支付我拖欠的学费吧
Consider it past-due tuition.
没有我你也能建立一番事业
Something tells me you would've figured it out without me.
再说了 让我的军士长 替我付钱也很奇怪
Besides, it's a little weird having my Master Sergeant carrying my tab.
我会还你的
I'll get us square.
- 晚安 内格利 - 晚安 雷彻
- Night, Neagley. - Night, Reacher.
给您 这是给您的
For you. Here you go.
- 请慢用 - 谢谢
Enjoy. Thank you.
好吧 敬一群活泼的人
Well, here's to a lively bunch.
你应该把你的班卓琴拿来
Should've brought your banjo.
等喝完这一轮 我要回会计部了
Well, I think after this round, I'm gonna head back to Accounting.
我还得完成一些文书工作
Still have some paperwork I need to finish.
但我们刚到这里
But we just got here.
我知道
I know.
如果您不介意我问的话 是谁派您来带这个小组的 长官
If you don't mind me asking, who directed you to field this team, sir?
我不介意你问 但我介意你叫我“长官”
I don't mind you asking. I do mind you calling me "sir."
您的级别比我高
You outrank me.
你是军士长 几乎每个人的级别都比你高
You're a Master Sergeant. Almost everyone outranks you.
你们不应该穿着制服喝酒
You're not supposed to be drinking in uniform.
我们没喝酒
We're not drinking.
我们之前在喝酒 但然后你打断了我们
We were drinking. Then you interrupted us.
她不属于这里
She doesn't belong here.
这里是军队 我们中有人属于这里吗
It's the Army. Do any of us really belong here?
- 你算是个聪明人吧  - 比你聪明
You some kind of smart guy? Smarter than you.
我也是个有规矩的人
I'm also a man with a rule.
人不犯我 我不犯人
People leave me and my pals alone, I leave them alone.
人若犯我 我必犯人
They don't, I don't.
我以为他的规矩是“一旦 打出第一枪 计划就见鬼去吧”
I thought his rule was plans go to hell when the first shot's fired.
这是军官俱乐部 不是给现役军人的
It's an officers' club. No enlisted.
我喝完啤酒就走 好吗 长官
How about I just finish my beer and I'll be on my way, okay, sir?
你安静点吧 大人在说话呢
How about you be quiet? There are adults are talking.
现在 要么她离开 要么我们把你们全都拽出去
Now it's either she leaves, or we drag you all out by your asses.
我给你个机会 因为我答应了我妈
I'm providing you an opening because I promised my mother
会给像你这样的蠢货一个脱身的机会
I'd give dumb guys like you a chance to walk away.
我们有12个人
We got 12.
你有九个
You got nine.
太可惜了
Well, that's a shame.
你再叫三个人来才有可能赢
You're at least three short.
不要挑衅我们
? Oh, don't give us none of your aggravation ?
我们受够了你的纪律
? We had it with your discipline ?
周六的夜晚...
? Saturday night's all right for fighting...
他锁我的头时 我以为我完了
I thought I was done when that guy got me in a headlock.
- 欠你一个人情 兄弟  - 是啊 兄弟
- Owe you one, brother. - Yeah, brother.
再给我拿点冰 我们就扯平了
Here, give me some more ice, call it even.
好的 热狗五分钟后上桌
All right, hot dogs are up in five.
点燃这支舞
? Gonna set this dance alight ?
因为周六的夜晚是我最爱的夜晚
? 'Cause Saturday night's the night I like ?
周六的夜晚没问题
? Saturday night's all right, all right,
没问题
all right ?
周六...
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday...
再来一瓶
Fresh one?
周六的夜晚没问题
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday ?
干杯
Cheers.
- 周六  - 周六
? Saturday, Saturday,
周六...
Saturday, Saturday...
我不应该去军官俱乐部的
You know, uh, I shouldn't've been at the officers' club.
周六
Saturday
我知道
I know.
那为什么要为这事打架
Then why get into a fight over it?
他语气不善
He didn't ask nicely.
周六
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday...
你和我会成为朋友的 不是吗 雷彻
You and I are gonna be pals, aren't we, Reacher?
周六
? Saturday, Saturday...
已经是朋友了 内格利
Already are, Neagley.
- 来吧  - 耶
好啊
饿吗
Hungry?
嘿
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
我就说一句
Real quick.
91团的男孩们今晚 学到了一个非常重要的教训
Tonight, the boys of the 91st learned a very important lesson.
他们学到了什么
And what did they learn?
不要惹特别调查员
That you do not mess with the Special Investigators!
You do not mess with the Special Investigators!
是啊
你知道今晚会发生这事
You knew that was gonna happen tonight.
我知道91团的人喜欢周四晚上喝酒
I knew the 91st like to drink on Thursday nights.
而且他们墨守成规
And that they're sticklers for the rules.
而且他们还是混蛋
And that they're assholes.
但现在 我知道他们能一起工作
But now... I know they can all work together.
合影留念 我们作为一个小组的第一天吧
Photo op to commemorate our first day as a unit.
你 去火边
You. Fire.
- 好的 - 去吧
- Go. - Okay.
- 我来照吧  - 我能处理 伙计
How about I just take it? Ah, no, man, I got it.
不行 你不能逃避照相 快来
No. No, you're not getting out of it that easy. Come on. Come on.
我能处理
I got this.
好的 各位 四秒钟
Okay, guys, four seconds.
- 小心你的骨质疏松 - 去你的 年轻人
Whoa, take it easy on your osteoporosis. Ah, kiss my ass, young blood.
好吧 夜色还早 斯旺
Okay, night's still young, Swan.
重新开始弹吉他吧 宝贝
Get back to strumming, baby.
《自由鸟》
"Free Bird"!
我才不干
Hell no.
不弹斯金纳德 齐柏林 亨德里克斯和谁人乐队的歌
No Skynyrd, no Zeppelin, no Hendrix, no Who.
我喜欢轻一点的音乐
I like my music lighter.
但不要害怕 我去撒个尿
But never fear, after I take a leak,
然后你们就能欣赏《鳄鱼摇滚》
you're about to get a little taste of "Crocodile Rock."
- 迫不及待了  - 嘿 雷彻
- Can't wait, can't wait. - Hey, Reacher.
他们把我从直升机上扔了下去 雷彻
They tossed me from a helicopter, Reacher.
你要怎么做
What are you gonna do about it?
欢迎来到洛杉矶国际机场
Welcome to Los Angeles International Airport.
乘客们 请准备好护照...
Passengers, please have passports ready...
芒特先生 您来访的原因是什么
Reason for your visit, Mr. Mount?
请叫我阿德里安 我是来观光的
Oh, Adrian, please. Um, I'm here to sightsee.
要去环球影城 星光大道 中国戏院
Universal Studios, Walk of Fame, Mann's Chinese.
我是个好莱坞狂热爱好者
You know, I'm a bit of an Old Hollywood fanatic.
有需要申报的东西吗
Anything to declare?
我没有需要申报的
I have nothing to declare.
祝您旅途愉快 先生
Enjoy your stay, sir.
护照
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
我们会跟你保持联系
We'll keep you posted.
安吉拉不知道 哪个邮政邮箱是卡尔文的
Angela has no idea which PO Box belonged to Calvin
在遗产处理完毕前 邮局不会告诉她
and the post office won't give her that information until the estate has been settled
因为邮箱是落在他公司的名义下的
because the box was in his company's name.
我们应该去他办公室看看邮箱吗
Should we check his office again for mail?
我们搜得很彻底了 那儿没有写着邮箱号码的东西
We were thorough. Nothing in there with a box number on it.
我们不能就这样进去试邮箱
We can't just go in there and start trying boxes.
他们会报警 而我们会被指控篡改邮件
They'll call the cops and we'll wind up with federal mail tampering charges.
我们要全面考虑
Then let's think this through.
跟世界上89%的人一样 弗朗茨是右撇子
Like 89% of the world, Franz is right-handed,
所以他可能会要一个进门右边的邮箱
so he probably asked for a box on the right when you enter.
人们喜欢自己更顺手的一边
Humans favor their dominant side.
他会收到发给他的公共记录 监控照片
He gets public records sent to him,
所以他需要一个大号的箱子
surveillance photos, so he's gonna need one of the big boxes.
我会从这些信息开始查
I'll start with them, see which one's packed with mail
看看哪个箱子里面装满了邮件 因为他有段时间没拿了
since Franz hasn't made a pickup in a while.
我只需要你分散他人注意力
I just need a distraction.
收到
Copy that.
嘿 你还好吗 艾伯特
Hey, how goes it... Albert?
我是个铁杆集邮迷
I am a hard-core philatelist
最近发行的这批邮票
and I have been fully aflutter about this new batch of stamps
让我非常激动
that were recently issued...
哪个系列的邮票
Which run?
我们有沙漠之花 州鸟和动漫世界
We've got, uh, Desert Flowers, uh, State Birds and the World of Anime.
全部都很感兴趣
All of 'em.
我口袋里有苏珊硬币 我准备好花掉这些钱了
I've got a bunch of Susan Bs jingling in my pocket and I'm ready to spend 'em.
好的
Um, okay.
至少有两打这样的卡通
There's at least two dozen of these, uh, cartoons.
不知道你熟不熟悉动漫 我觉得是日本的
If you're not familiar with anime, I believe it's Japanese.
好家伙
You don't say.
州鸟非常惊人
Oh, and uh... the State Birds are spectacular.
但永远都集不齐五十种
But never gonna get 50 different species.
西部草地鹨代表了六个不同的州
The Western Meadowlark represents six different states.
不好意思 能让我开我的邮箱吗
Excuse me. Excuse me. Can I get to my box?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
先生 那是你的钥匙吗
Sir, is that your key?
是的 我只是想不起来 哪个箱子是我的了
Yeah, I just... can't remember which box is mine.
先生 这个人在用不属于他的钥匙
Sir, this man is using a key that isn't his.
- 你是邮政警察吗  - 需要帮忙吗
- What are you, the mail police? - Sir, can I help you?
- 之前邮件被偷过 - 能给我看看花的吗
Could you show me the Flowers, Al?
- 先生  - 这里一切安好
Sir. All good here.
不 我需要您的身份证件 确保您是那个箱子的主人
No, sir, I'm gonna need some ID that ties you to that box.
我全都要 怎么样
You know what? I'll take all of them. How about that?
好了
Here we go.
没事 我只是忘了是哪个箱子了
No problem. Just got my boxes confused.
你知道怎么着 艾尔 算了吧
You know what, Al? I think I'll pass.
都是什么东西
What do we got?
账单 请求
Bills, solicitations...
潜在线索
Potential.
看来你的“邮局直觉”是对的
Looks like your post office hunch worked.
我说过你很聪明吗 内格利
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley?
- 还远远不够 - 我们得看看这里面有什么
Not nearly enough. We need to see what's on this.
该死 我的笔记本的端口不同
Damn it. My laptop has a different port.
我得去拿个适配器
I got to go pick up an adapter.
帮我个忙 用手机软件叫辆出租车
Do me a favor. Order up a ride on one of those phone app things.
我得借用你的车
I need to borrow your car.
你知道是这个U盘害死弗朗茨的
You know Franz was killed over this hard drive
现在你想去拿把枪
and now you want to go get a gun.
是的
Yup.
但首先 我需要去教堂
But first... I need to go to church.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我想知道我能否寻求帮助
I was wondering if I could ask for some help.
我们就是给人提供帮助的
Well, that is what we give here.
我在找我的表弟
I'm looking for my cousin.
他有很严重的吸毒问题
He has a really bad drug problem
一个朋友说看见他住在附近的街道上
and a family friend said they saw him living on the street around here.
- 很遗憾听到这个消息 - 谢谢
I'm sorry to hear that. Well, thank you.
我答应过姑姑 不带上她儿子就不回家
I promised my aunt I wouldn't come back home without her son.
我甚至都不知道从哪里开始找
I don't know where to even begin looking.
我想也许教堂有个支持小组之类的
And I thought maybe the church has a support group or something, and... through that,
也许可以通过这种小组 了解吉米在哪里买的毒品
maybe you'd have some idea where Jimmy was scoring?
恶魔创造那种毒药的时候 已经尽了全力 不是吗
The devil did his best work when he created that poison, didn't he?
确实
Sure did.
几乎每个参加我们外展计划的人
Almost everyone who comes in to our outreach program
都是从同一个地方得到“慰藉”的
gets their fix from the same place:
那就是洛克威以东的杜蒙特
Dumont, just east of Rockaway.
但你一个人过去 简直是自寻死路 孩子
But you've got to have a death wish to walk in there alone, son.
我会没事的 神父
I'll be fine, Father.
正义在我这边
I have righteousness on my side.
再多一点
Little extra taste?
我明天会给你带回来
I'll get you back tomorrow?
这不是家具仓库 伙计
This ain't no furniture warehouse, man.
我可不做“公益活动”
I don't do no credit.
在我决定从沙发上起来前给我滚
Get the fuck out of here before I decide to get off my couch, man.
朝我们开过来的傻子是谁
Yo, who's this fool pulling up?
见鬼
Oh, shit!
混蛋疯子
Crazy motherfucker.
可卡因 氧可酮 冰毒 各种毒品应有尽有
Cocaine, Oxy, meth. Full service dealer.
你是谁 混蛋
Motherfucker.
别管我是谁
Don't mind me.
我会拿走这个
I'll be taking this.
还有这个
And this.
这是给外展计划的
For the outreach program.
条形码很完美
Bar codes are perfect.
全息图很立体
Holograms, bulletproof.
- 钱在包里  - 请自便
Money in the bag? Help yourself.
六位数仪器在前面
Six-figure instruments are in the front.
我第一次听说无记名债券 是在《比佛利山庄警察》里
First time I heard about bearer bonds was Beverly Hills Cop.
我不知道这是真的还是电影里杜撰的
I didn't know if they were real or Hollywood bullshit.
你可以为他们点亮一座灯塔 水印完好无损
You could shine a lighthouse on 'em, man. Watermarks are flawless.
没人会知道你是谁
No one'll really know who you really are.
但你知道
But you know.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 刚回来  - 是的
- Just getting back? - Yeah.
我不得不去了三家店 才买到我想要的东西 你呢
Had to go to three stores to get what I needed. You?
- 一个地方就搞定了我要的所有东西 - 那可真好
Got everything I needed in one place. Bet you did.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
我看到你还在用铜指虎
See you're still using brass knuckles.
不用弹簧刀了
No more switchblade?
往下看
Look down.
嘿 奥唐纳
Hey, O'Donnell.
嘿 内格利
Hey, Neagley.
别指责我弄乱了房间 我发现时已经成这样了
Don't blame me for this shithole. I found it like this.
我当时跟我家人在一起
I was with my family.
那周是不插电周
It was, uh, Unplugged Week.
听起来很可怕
That sounds awful.
可不是嘛
No shit.
每年一次 我老婆给我们 在一个偏僻的地方租了一间小屋
Once a year, my wife makes us get a cabin in the middle of nowhere,
没有手机 没有设备 没有电视
no cell phones, no devices, no TVs.
远离屏幕 亲近自然
Less screens, more greens.
理论上很好 但到了第三天 我的恶魔孩子们就想互相残杀
Good in theory, till by the third day my devil children want to kill each other.
我回到家 检查了语音信箱 尽快赶到了这里
So, I got home, checked the voice mail, got here as quick as I could.
那混蛋把我的牙刷折成了两半
Assholes snapped my toothbrush in half.
现在我一无所有了
Now I own nothing.
很高兴你没变
Glad to see you haven't changed.
你变了
You have.
家庭度假 老婆奴
Family vacations. Wife telling you what to do.
不是我记忆中性欲过剩的堕落者了
Not the oversexed degenerate I remember.
我被驯化了
I've been domesticated.
显然是的
Apparently.
我得说 弗朗茨的事让我很生气
Got to say, pretty pissed about this whole Franzy thing.
我很爱那孩子
Kind of loved that kid.
所以我们要杀谁呢
So... who we killing over it?
你什么时候重回T台了
When are you due back on the catwalk?
你看到你穿着跟那个无家可归的
God, you must've been mortified when you saw
在后面的咖啡罐里拉屎的人 一样的衣服一定觉得很羞愧吧
you were wearing the same clothes as the homeless guy taking a shit in a coffee can out back.
见鬼 密码保护
Shit. Password protected.
- 我讨厌猜密码 - 即将更讨厌猜
Hate guessing passwords. About to hate it more.
它已经设置好了 所以我们得在 两分钟内试三次 否则U盘会被删除
Franz set it up so we get three guesses in two minutes or the drive's erased.
它会随着新设备自动启动
And it auto-launched once it recognized a new device.
- 你在搞我吧 - 没
- You got to be shitting me. - Nope.
所以我们要像分析罪犯一样 分析弗朗茨
Okay, so we got to break Franzy down like we'd profile a perp.
密码来自于内心深处
Passwords come from deep down.
弗朗茨的特点是什么  他因什么而出名
What was Franzy's thing? What was he known for?
- 因聪明而出名 - 是啊 但我们都很聪明
Being smart. Yeah, but we were all pretty smart.
匹兹堡 他总说起那里
Pittsburgh? That's all the guy talked about.
海盗队 钢人队 那家把薯条放在面上的三明治店
Pirates, Steelers, that, uh, that sandwich place where they put the fries on top.
- 普利曼迪兄弟 - 对
- Primanti Brothers. - That was it.
不是匹兹堡本身 是他对它的忠诚
Yeah, but not Pittsburgh in and of itself. It was his loyalty to it.
弗朗茨是个忠诚的人
Franz was a loyal guy.
这么多年来一直很喜欢110组 他还教他的孩子们我们的口号
Still loved the 110th after all these years, taught his kid our slogan.
记得他声称1979年的海盗队
Do you remember when he used to claim
比1978年的洋基队更好
that the Pirates of '79 were better than the Yankees of '78?
他们比赛的时候 他都还没出生呢 而他还在那儿吵
I mean, the little shit wasn't even alive when those teams played and he'd still argue his ass off.
但忠诚是个副产品 忠诚从何而来
Okay, but loyalty is a byproduct. Where does it come from?
英雄崇拜 尊重
Hero worship. Respect.
如果他尊重一个人 他就不会被旁人所左右
If Franz respected someone, he couldn't be dissuaded.
海盗队是最厉害的队伍 迈尔斯戴维斯是最伟大的音乐家
Pirates were the greatest team ever. Miles Davis was the greatest musician ever.
- 弗朗茨忠于他尊重的人和事 - 就是这个 你说对了
Franz was loyal to what he respected. That's it. You got it.
罗伯特克莱门特
Roberto Clemente.
他会只用姓氏
He'd only use the last name.
等等 威利斯塔格尔呢
Wait! What about Willie Stargell?
威利斯塔格尔在给地震灾民 运送物资时死于飞机失事吗
Did Willie Stargell die in a plane crash delivering supplies to earthquake victims?
是克莱门特
It's Clemente.
不 不是
No, it isn't.
- 谁会用这种设备  - 弗朗茨 正是因为这个原因
Who would use a device like this? Franz. For this very reason.
我会试试迈尔斯戴维斯 弗朗茨很崇拜这家伙
I'm gonna try Miles Davis. Franz worshipped the guy.
很好的猜测 大胆试试吧
Good a guess as any. Go for it.
- 不对 - 见鬼
Nope. Shit.
这就是为何我讨厌猜密码
This is why I hate guessing passwords.
我很不想提出这个建议
Oh, this makes me sick to even suggest this,
走出这个房间 我会否认这种说法
and outside of this room I'll deny ever saying it,
但比起任何球员 艺术家 他最尊重的人是谁
but who did Franz respect more than anyone? Any ballplayer, any artist?
他崇拜的英雄是谁
Who did he hero worship?
别添乱
Get the hell out of here.
进入110组的前几周 他剪了跟你一样的发型
A few weeks into the 110th, the kid started cutting his hair like you,
像你一样说话 跟着你 他想成为你
talking like you, following you around. He wanted to be you, Reacher.
最好确认输入吧 我们时间不多了
You better punch that. We're running out of time.
王八蛋
Son of a bitch.
别自以为是
Don't go getting a big head.
是啊
你好
Hello.
你想要这个吗
Would you like this?
你知道我为何那么喜欢漫画书吗
Now, do you know why I love comic books so much?
因为好人总能获胜
Because the good guys always win.
麦克布莱德先生 您预订了飞往丹佛的航班
Mr. McBride? You're booked for your flight to Denver.
- 祝您旅途愉快 - 谢谢 一定会愉快的
Enjoy your trip. Thank you. I certainly will.
姓名:安德鲁麦克布莱德
“安德鲁麦克布莱德 艾伦梅森 亚历杭德罗门蒂斯 亚历山大...”
Andrew McBride. Alan Mason. Alejandro Mendez. Alexander Markopoulos.
只是一个名单 其中所有名字的首字母都是AM
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials A.M.
全是化名 你保留同样的首字母 这样你的签名永远都不会变
All aliases. You keep the same initials so your signature never has to change.
就一个“A”加一个带波浪线的“M” 无论化名具体是什么
Just an A and an M with a squiggle after it, no matter which pseudonym you're using.
至少你那部分内容还能读出来
Well, at least you can read yours.
我刚得到的是一页又一页的随机数据
I've just got page after page of random numbers.
- 没有顺序 没有意义 什么都没 - 至少我们觉得没有 而且暂时而已
No order. No meaning. Nothing. At least to us. For now.
无论这是什么 它害死了弗朗茨
Well, whatever this shit is, it was enough to get Franz killed,
还害得你们的房间被毁 天知道我们还不知道些什么
your rooms trashed, and God knows whatever else we don't know about.
这些人可不会手软
These guys aren't shy about getting aggressive.
- 我们需要更多人力 - 我不愿承认 但他说得对
We need more manpower. Hate to say it, but he's right.
110组的人都联系不上
None of the 110th are reachable.
我们每年都给斯旺寄圣诞贺卡
Well, we send a Christmas card to Swan every year.
我想他现在住在皇后区
I think he lives in Queens now.
我会让莉莉查看我们的假期邮件列表
I'll have Lilly check our holiday mailer list.
- 怎么了  - 你真的被驯化了
What? You really are domesticated.
里面没有任何噪音 一点纽约背景音乐
No noise coming from inside. A little New York background music?
卡洛 你妈说你得回家吃饭
Yo, Carlo! Your mom says you got to be home for dinner!
你们闻到了吗
Oh. You smell that?
我去楼上
I'll take the upstairs.
在这里
In here.
颈圈上写着:“麦丝”
Collar says Maisi.
它把马桶水喝干了
Drank the toilet bowl dry.
脱水而亡 这种死法太痛苦了
Dehydration. That's a tough way to die.
斯旺永远不会让狗渴死
Swan would never let a dog die of thirst.
如果他不回家 那只有一种可能
The only way he doesn't come home is if he couldn't come home.
斯旺死了
Swan's dead.
先是弗朗茨 现在是斯旺
Franzy, now Swan...
我们也联系不上团队其他成员
We can't get ahold of the other team members, either.
老大
Boss?
你有什么想法
What are you thinking?
少校
Major?
我觉得有人一心想干掉特别调查员
I'm thinking there's someone hellbent on taking out the Special Investigators.
他们是冲我们来的
And they're coming after us.
很好
Good.
字幕翻译: 匡思颖
创意监督 朝思